<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Renlord Yang on Renlord&#39;s Webpage</title>
    <link>https://renlord.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Renlord Yang on Renlord&#39;s Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://renlord.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AS204710 is live, long live the Zippy Kangaroo</title>
      <link>https://renlord.com/posts/2022-06-15-as204710-is-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renlord.com/posts/2022-06-15-as204710-is-live/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve recently just set up an IPv6-only AS called Zippy Kangaroo.
I broadcast my IPv6 prefixes from my home server cluster. So far, only supporting ICMP.
Hoping to run more services.
I&amp;rsquo;m looking for fellow ASes to peer with!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forwarding DNS queries over TLS on Tor</title>
      <link>https://renlord.com/posts/2021-09-26-dns-over-tls-over-tor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renlord.com/posts/2021-09-26-dns-over-tls-over-tor/</guid>
      <description>DNS query metadata can leak a lot of information about your internet activities. While DNS-over-TLS/HTTPS has definitely improved DNS privacy over the years, DNS requests can still be associated with user identity at the resolver by logging the origin IP address of the DNS query request. DNS-over-TLS-over-Tor addresses this vulnerability as Tor circuits masquerade the origin of the DNS request.
Cloudflare deployed its DNS resolver as a Tor Hidden Service back in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CopperheadOS Bogus Legal Threat</title>
      <link>https://renlord.com/posts/2020-03-25-copperheados-legal-threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renlord.com/posts/2020-03-25-copperheados-legal-threat/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago I received legal threats from CopperheadOS alledging that I have infringed their copyright when I&amp;rsquo;ve personally made contributions to the Graphene OS project. These accusations are invalid and have no legal basis whatsoever as the copyright of the cited code belongs to Daniel Micay who is the project owner of Graphene OS.
I have released these legal letters (sent to both myself personally and my academic institution, The University of Melbourne) in the public domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apk Packages I use on Graphene OS</title>
      <link>https://renlord.com/posts/2020-01-10-grapheneos-compatible-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renlord.com/posts/2020-01-10-grapheneos-compatible-apps/</guid>
      <description>List of apk packages (works well!) I install on GrapheneOS:
com.nextcloud.client com.tananaev.logcat org.mian.gitnex com.aurora.adroid fr.acinq.eclair.wallet.mainnet2 com.devhd.feedly org.liberty.android.freeotpplus com.whatsapp com.transferwise.android [3] com.forrestguice.suntimeswidget org.sufficientlysecure.keychain org.schabi.newpipe im.vector.alpha au.com.nab.mobile com.vonglasow.michael.satstat com.sigmarelax.doitoscihub com.reddit.frontpage ca.rmen.android.networkmonitor org.connectbot com.secuso.privacyFriendlyCodeScanner com.waze au.gov.customs.trs org.thoughtcrime.securesms com.aurora.store au.com.selfwealth.mobile au.com.qantas.qantas com.alienpants.leafpicrevived at.bitfire.davdroid com.sonos.acr net.sourceforge.opencamera com.google.android.apps.maps org.dmfs.tasks com.samourai.sentinel au.com.realestate.app [2] com.github.axet.callrecorder com.tranzmate org.videolan.vlc com.windyty.android com.greenaddress.greenbits_android_wallet com.fsck.k9 ws.xsoh.etar com.valvesoftware.android.steam.community com.ink.jetstar.mobile.app com.digitalbitbox.tfa com.zeapo.pwdstore com.google.android.inputmethod.pinyin org.jellyfin.mobile com.logitech.ueboom au.com.medibank.phs com.stackexchange.marvin net.skyscanner.android.main net.osmand.plus com.wireguard.android de.danoeh.antennapod com.github.gotify app.attestation.auditor com.getpocketbook [3] it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Multiarch Builds Quick and Easy</title>
      <link>https://renlord.com/posts/2019-11-09-docker-multiarch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renlord.com/posts/2019-11-09-docker-multiarch/</guid>
      <description>As you all known from my things page, I run a multiarch cluster of nodes to run a variety of my services. More often than not, service images provided by maintainers only support x86 and x86_64 architectures. As a consequence of this, I have to self-build my service images.
When it was just building for one type of architecture (i.e. arm32) for my Odroid XU4, it was not so bad. Once I added another node, my arm64 Odroid-N2, it started to become a hassle to manually author custom Dockerfiles to build for each architecture by hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://renlord.com/google29121bf6dbd9149a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renlord.com/google29121bf6dbd9149a/</guid>
      <description>google-site-verification: google29121bf6dbd9149a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading</title>
      <link>https://renlord.com/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renlord.com/reading/</guid>
      <description>Reading My personal collection of reading material.
Systems General Systems Latency Numbers every programmer should know What Systems Researchers Need to Know about NAND Flash What Every Programmer Should Know About Memory Mobile Devices An Analysis of Power Consumption in a Smartphone Android The Android Platform Security Model Inspirational The Fable of the Dragon-Tyrant The illustrated guide to a Ph.D. Books Algorithms to Live By: The Computer Science of Human Decisions 👍 Bad Blood: Secrets and Lies in a Silicon Valley Startup 🤓 Capital in the Twenty-First Century 🤓 Capital and Idealogy 🍿 Chaos Monkeys: Obscene Fortune and Random Failure in Silicon Valley 👍Immune: A Journey Into the Mysterious System That Keeps You Alive &amp;mdash; Video Trailer by Kurzgesagt Lifespan: Why We Age—and Why We Don&amp;rsquo;t Have To 😌 Love for Imperfect Things: How to Accept Yourself in a World Striving for Perfection Permanant Record 🍿 The Dictators&amp;rsquo; Handbook &amp;mdash; Video Trailer by CGP Grey The Happiness Hypothesis: Finding Modern Truth in Ancient Wisdom 👍 &amp;mdash; Good read, interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things</title>
      <link>https://renlord.com/things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renlord.com/things/</guid>
      <description>Things Last Updated: 16.02.2023
Communication I use the following chat services (in order of personal preference):
Signal Apple iMessages Whatsapp Bitcoin You know what Bitcoin is, but how does it work?. 3blue1brown (Grant Sanderson) on Youtube explains it best. How secure is Bitcoin? A numerical explanation, again by 3blue1brown (Grant Sanderson) on Youtube.
Services and Hardware I self-host a good number of services on my inexpensive private cluster of ARM single-board computers (SBCs) and a x86 NUC.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
